<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cores:Collection on Awesome resources for Hardware Description</title>
    <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/categories/corescollection/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cores:Collection on Awesome resources for Hardware Description</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://hdl.github.io/awesome/categories/corescollection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>fusesoc</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/fusesoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/fusesoc/</guid>
      <description>FuseSoC is a package manager and a set of build tools for HDL code. Its main purpose is to increase reuse of IP cores and be an aid for creating, building and simulating SoC solutions. FuseSoC provides utilities for:
 reusing existing cores creating compile-time or run-time configurations running regression tests against multiple simulators porting designs to new targets leting other projects use your code  References:
 fusesoc-cores: FuseSoC standard core library tiny-cores: Collection of assorted small cores edalize was part of FuseSoC FuseSoc is the continuation of ORPSoC  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LibreCores</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/librecores/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/librecores/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot; Digital devices are the basic building blocks of electronic systems. Such devices are for application-specific devices like a USB controller. But also programmable System-on-Chip are found in embedded systems. Both tastes of a chip are composed of basic building blocks, so called IP (Intellectual Property) cores. A &amp;ldquo;LibreCore&amp;rdquo; is such an IP core that is created and distributed in the open source spirit. And LibreCores.org is like a good neighborhood pub, a place to meet the community and —most importantly— find such cores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenCores</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/opencores/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/opencores/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;OpenCores is the most prominent online community for the development of gateware IP (Intellectual Properties) Cores. It is the place where such cores are shared and promoted in the spirit of Free and Open Source collaboration.&amp;quot;
&amp;ldquo;The OpenCores portal hosts the source code for different digital gateware projects and supports the users’ community providing a platform for listing, presenting, and managing such projects; together with version control systems for sources management.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
