<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>parser on Awesome resources for Hardware Description</title>
    <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/tags/parser/</link>
    <description>Recent content in parser on Awesome resources for Hardware Description</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hdl.github.io/awesome/tags/parser/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>pyVHDLParser</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/pyvhdlparser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/pyvhdlparser/</guid>
      <description>Main Goals  Parsing  Slice an input document into tokens and text blocks which are categorized in groups for fast indexing. reserve case, whitespace and comments. Recover on parsing errors Good error reporting / throw exceptions   Fast Processing  Multi-pass parsing and analysis Delay analysis if not needed for current pass Link tokens and blocks for fast-forward scanning (triple helix)   Generic VHDL Language Model  Assemble a sourcecode document-object-model (Code-DOM) Provide an API for code introspection Provide an API for code modification / transformation    Use Cases  Generate documentation by using the fast-forward scanner Generate a document/language model by using the grouped text-block scanner Extract compile orders and other dependency graphs Generate highlighted syntax  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GHDL</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/ghdl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/ghdl/</guid>
      <description>Open-source analyzer, compiler, simulator and (experimental) synthesizer for VHDL, a Hardware Description Language (HDL). GHDL is not an interpreter: it allows you to analyse and elaborate sources to generate machine code from your design. Native program execution is the only way for high speed simulation.
Full support for the 1987, 1993, 2002 versions of the IEEE 1076 VHDL standard, and partial for the latest 2008 revision. Partial support of PSL. Can write waveforms to a GHW, VCD or FST file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ghdl-yosys-plugin</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/ghdl-yosys-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/ghdl-yosys-plugin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a long description&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hdlConvertor</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/hdlconvertor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/hdlconvertor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a long description&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rust_hdl</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/rust_hdl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/rust_hdl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a long description&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
