<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>framework on Awesome resources for Hardware Description</title>
    <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/tags/framework/</link>
    <description>Recent content in framework on Awesome resources for Hardware Description</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://hdl.github.io/awesome/tags/framework/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Open Source VHDL Verification Methodology (OSVVM)</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/osvvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/osvvm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Open Source VHDL Verification Methodology (OSVVM) provides an ASIC level VHDL verification methodology that is simple enough to use even on small FPGA projects. OSVVM offers the same capabilities as those based on other verification languages:&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SVUnit</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/svunit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/svunit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;SVUnit is an open-source test framework for ASIC and FPGA developers writing Verilog/SystemVerilog code. SVUnit is automated, fast, lightweight and easy to use making it the only SystemVerilog test framework in existence suited to both design and verification engineers that aspire to high quality code and low bug rates.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Universal VHDL Verification Methodology (UVVM)</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/uvvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/uvvm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Open Source VHDL Verification Library and Methodology - for very efficient VHDL verification of FPGA and ASIC - resulting also in a significant quality improvement&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VUnit</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/vunit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/vunit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;VUnit is an open source unit testing framework for VHDL/SystemVerilog [&amp;hellip;]  It features the functionality needed to realize continuous and automated testing of your HDL code. VUnit doesn’t replace but rather complements traditional testing methodologies by supporting a “test early and often” approach through automation.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
