<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conferences on Awesome resources for Hardware Description</title>
    <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/categories/conferences/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conferences on Awesome resources for Hardware Description</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://hdl.github.io/awesome/categories/conferences/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CHIPS Alliance Workshops and Meetings</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/chips-workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/chips-workshops/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LATTE: Languages, Tools, and Techniques for Accelerator Design</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/latte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/latte/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;LATTE is an ASPLOS workshop on applying programming languages and compilers techniques to generate hardware accelerators.&amp;quot;
There is a GitHub repository with discussion threads for each paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Design Automation (OSDA)</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/osda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/osda/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;This one-day workshop aims to bring together industrial, academic, and hobbyist actors to explore, disseminate, and network over ongoing efforts for open design automation, with a view to enabling unfettered research and development, improving EDA quality, and lowering the barriers and risks to entry for industry. These aims are particularly poignant due to the recent efforts across the European Union (and beyond) that mandate &amp;lsquo;open access&amp;rsquo; for publicly funded research to both published manuscripts as well as any code necessary for reproducing its conclusions.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORConf</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/orconf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/orconf/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;ORConf is an annual conference for open source digital, semiconductor and embedded systems designers and users. Each year attendees are treated to an ever-impressive array of presentations from all corners of the open source hardware space.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
