<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tools:Managers on Awesome resources for Hardware Description</title>
    <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/categories/toolsmanagers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tools:Managers on Awesome resources for Hardware Description</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://hdl.github.io/awesome/categories/toolsmanagers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>edalize</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/edalize/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/edalize/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Edalize is a Python Library for interacting with EDA tools. It can create project files for supported tools and run them in batch or GUI mode (where supported).&amp;quot;
&amp;ldquo;All EDA tools such as Icarus, Yosys, ModelSim, Vivado, Verilator, GHDL, Quartus etc get input HDL files (Verilog and VHDL) and some tool-specific files (constraint files, memory initialization files, IP description files etc). Together with the files, perhaps a couple of Verilog defines, some top-level parameters/generics or some tool-specific options are set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HDLmake</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/hdlmake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/hdlmake/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A tool designed to help FPGA designers to manage and share their HDL code by automatically finding file dependencies, writing synthesis &amp;amp; simulation Makefiles, and fetching IP-Core libraries from remote repositories
 Synthesis Makefile generation Simulation Makefile generation HDL parser and dependency solver GIT/SVN Support Multiple HDL Languages Multiple Tools Multiple Operating Systems&amp;rdquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pyFPGA</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/pyfpga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/pyfpga/</guid>
      <description>PyFPGA is a Python Class for vendor-independent FPGA development. It allows using a single project file and programmatically executing synthesis, implementation, generation of bitstream and/or transference to supported boards.
 The workflow is command-line centric. It&amp;rsquo;s friendly with Version Control Systems and Continuous Integration (CI). Allows reproducibility and repeatability. Consumes fewer system resources than GUI based workflows.  Also, some command-line helpers are provided, for quick tests or small projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pyIPCMI</title>
      <link>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/pyipcmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hdl.github.io/awesome/items/pyipcmi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a long description&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
